perkspot.com 2019-02-07

# Privacy Policy | PerkSpot Documentation

The following privacy policy governs your use of the PerkSpot service, operated by 12 Interactive LLC ("We") on behalf of your employer or organization.

## I. Purpose and Who We Are

12 Interactive LLC is a limited liability corporation with a principal place of business at 216 W. Ohio St., Chicago, IL 60654. If you reside or are located in the European Economic Area ("EEA") 12 Interactive LLC is the data controller of all Personally Identifiable Information (as defined below) collected via the Site and of certain Personally Identifiable Information collected from third parties, as set out in this Privacy Policy.

We are committed to protecting your privacy. At no time will we trade, sell, or distribute for free organization-specific or personal information, including email addresses or other user IDs, to any individual, company, vendor or organization, in ways other than disclosed in this privacy statement.

This privacy statement covers the site www.perkspot.com and private label sub-domains delivered by 12 Interactive LLC, (i.e. abc.perkspot.com, etc.). Because 12 Interactive LLC wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices.

The PerkSpot service is a portal through which users access discounts redeemable at selected vendors. In some cases, online purchases facilitated by the PerkSpot portal are subject to the privacy policies of the website where that transaction is conducted, whose policies may differ from those that govern PerkSpot. 

## II. Information We Collect

### Personal Information

Your first name, last name, email address, and location represent the only pieces of personal information required to access PerkSpot. In certain instances, other demographic data will be collected but is not required.

Purchases on our website or through vendors may require the collection of billing information such as address, phone numbers, credit card numbers, and banking information.

Your information may also include preferences, other demographic or anonymous usage data.

### Website Data and Cookies

PerkSpot collects click-stream data and other preference information in order to improve the function and vendor selection of the service for you or for others. (Click-stream data represents a page-by-page history of a person’s service usage.)

We use (or may use) cookies and web beacons when you visit our Site. For more information on our use of cookies and web beacons, please refer to our Cookies Policy.

### Customer Service Contacts and Feedback

Personal information is gathered to ensure a prompt and accurate reply by a PerkSpot representative, as well as other vendors and service providers. You may also have the option to provide feedback on services.

### Employer, Employment, Organization and Membership Data

You, your employer, or organization may provide data to us, such your status as an employee and other personal information.

## III. How Information is Used

PerkSpot uses this information to provide the benefits/services associated with the program.

### By PerkSpot

PerkSpot uses your information to provide the service to you and customize the service to your interests. Your information is used for customer service purposes to resolve any issues. Your information can be used to contact you for legal, regulatory, compliance, and other similar business needs related to the service.

Although your privacy is of paramount concern to us, PerkSpot cannot reasonably be expected to suppress information where the withholding of such information represents a violation of federal or state law.

PerkSpot reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information – including email address – as required by law and when it is believed that disclosure is necessary to protect PerkSpots’s rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on the site(s).

### Vendors on PerkSpot

We take measures to protect your privacy and your right to only be contacted with your permission. Your information is only shared in the following cases:

  * For customer service purposes, we may share your information, including personally-identifiable information, with vendors and other service providers in the interest of resolving an issue.
  * Information that is not personally-identifiable may be shared with vendors in order to improve your shopping experience. This may include information such as your shopping preferences, ZIP code, employer or member organization, so that relevant offers and discounts may be shown to you.
  * We may share your personally identifiable information with reputable vendors so they may further customize and simplify your shopping experience. To be eligible, vendors must commit in writing that they will not use your information in any way beyond supporting your shopping experience or fulfillment of purchases. This information will never be sold or used for any marketing purposes without your explicit consent.

Please note that our service links to vendor websites and your use of those vendor websites are governed by those vendors without direct control or jurisdiction by us or this policy. Each vendor maintains its own privacy policy that you should be familiar with before you submit your personal information. Our privacy policy is not applicable on any of the vendor sites. Therefore, it is important for a potential buyer to familiarize themselves with the privacy policies of each vendor.

### Your Employer or Organization

We do not share your personally-identifiable information with your employer or organization.

### For Statistical and Analytical Purposes

Your information may be combined with others or anonymized to provide insights into the use of the service including user enrollment and use. This anonymous or aggregated data may be shared with vendors, employers, organizations, and others with an interest in our service.

### Technology and Service Providers

We partner with reputable service and technology providers to deliver our service. Your information may be transmitted to them and stored on their servers; however, your information, along with our own company secrets and software, is considered confidential. Providers have no rights to your information.

PerkSpot may use an outside company to fulfill orders and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes unless explicitly disclosed to you.

## IV. Retention of Personally Identifiable Information

The length of time we retain Personally Identifiable Information depends on the purposes for which we collect and use it and/or as required to comply with applicable laws and to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights.

We adhere to GDPR guidelines, meaning we make the following commitments to users residing or located in the EEA, and strive to make the same available to others where possible: Personally Identifiable Information is retained for no longer than necessary for the purposes for which the Personally Identifiable Information is processed.

## V. Updating or Deleting Your Personally Identifiable Information

We adhere to GDPR guidelines, meaning we make the following commitments to users residing or located in EEA, and strive to make the same available to others where possible:

You can access your Personally Identifiable Information and confirm that it remains correct and up-to-date or choose whether or not you wish to receive material from us or some of our partners by logging into the Site and visiting your user account page.

If you would like further information in relation to your rights or would like to exercise any of them, you may also contact us via cs@perkspot.com.You have the right to request that we:

  * provide access to any Personally Identifiable Information we hold about you;
  * prevent the processing of your Personally Identifiable Information for direct-marketing purposes;
  * update any Personally Identifiable Information which is out of date or incorrect;
  * delete any Personally Identifiable Information which we are holding about you;
  * restrict the way that we process your Personally Identifiable Information;
  * provide your Personally Identifiable Information to a third party provider of services; or
  * provide you with a copy of any Personally Identifiable Information which we hold about you.

We try to answer every email promptly where possible, and provide our response within the time period stated by applicable law. Keep in mind, however, that there will be residual information that will remain within our databases, access logs and other records, which may or may not contain your Personally Identifiable Information. Please also note that certain Personally Identifiable Information may be exempt from such requests in certain circumstances, which may include if we need to keep processing your Personally Identifiable Information to comply with a legal obligation.

When you email us with a request, we may ask that you provide us with information necessary to confirm your identity.

## VI. Our Protection Safeguards

We respect your privacy and take precautions to ensure your safety as a user of our service. We strive to treat your personal information with the same standard of care we use with our own personal data. While we cannot protect from every eventuality, we take measures to protect the service and your data from theft, corruption, misuse, illegal action, or other malfeasance.

We assign a special standard of care to personally-identifiable information for the purpose of protecting your privacy and to make it difficult for anyone to contact you without your permission.

Within our company, access to your information is restricted to those with a business need to be able to access it. We employ additional safeguards including encryption, physical controls, and two-factor authentication to restrict access to your information.

When selecting vendors to participate in the service, we consider their history and reputation with regard to consumer privacy and data protection.

### Communication Practices

#### Opt Out

At any time, users may opt out of PerkSpot related correspondence by sending an email to cs@perkspot.com. Users may also access their personal information, including email address, to make edits in the “My Account” section of the website.

Requests are honored as immediately as possible, but may take up to five days.

#### Retained Email

When you opt-out of communications, your email address and some data is retained, but only for these specific purposes:

  * To retain a record of your opt-out, so that no one can sign-up again with your email address.
  * To continue to deliver our service obligations to you and your employer or organization, such as access to employer listings, prior purchases, and other features.
  * To administer our legal, regulatory, compliance, and other similar business responsibilities.

## VII. Notification of Changes to this Policy

Users will be notified of changes or revisions to this privacy policy, including our email practices, by a notice posted on the login page of PerkSpot. The notice will contain a link, whereby the privacy policy can be examined in full. In this way, registered users are made aware of policy changes prior to shopping or browsing the website. As always, a user who is not amenable to the conditions of a revised privacy policy may opt out of PerkSpot by the means outlined earlier in this document.

## VIII. Your Consent

As a user of PerkSpot, you consent to our collection and storage of your personal information, including email address, (as defined above) in our database, and to our use of aggregated and non-personal information generated by the viewing habits of our users. We store your personal information on servers located in the United States of America. By agreeing to this Privacy Policy, you give your consent for us to do so.

## IX. Contact Information

Questions or comments regarding this Policy should be submitted to PerkSpot by mail to:

PerkSpot  
216 W Ohio St.  
Floor 4  
Chicago, IL 60654 

Or by email to 12 Interactive Customer Service ([cs@perkspot.com](mailto:cs@perkspot.com))

EFFECTIVE DATE: October 4rd, 2018
